<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fnsefaq on Friends of North Shore Elementary</title>
    <link>/tags/fnsefaq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fnsefaq on Friends of North Shore Elementary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:06:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/fnsefaq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the best way to stay informed?</title>
      <link>/questions/fnse/what-is-the-best-way-to-stay-informed-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/fnse/what-is-the-best-way-to-stay-informed-/</guid>
      <description>Follow us on Facebook and attend our monthly meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When are meetings held?</title>
      <link>/questions/fnse/when-are-meetings-held-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/fnse/when-are-meetings-held-/</guid>
      <description>FNSE meets approximately every month at the Panera on 4th St. in St. Petersburg. Meetings last from 7:30-9pm where we get updates on different committee events, projects, and needs as well as strategize about how to move forward together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How has FNSE contributed so far?</title>
      <link>/questions/fnse/how-has-fnse-contributed-so-far-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/fnse/how-has-fnse-contributed-so-far-/</guid>
      <description>To date FNSE has been able to contribute time, talent and treasure to North Shore Elementary. Some of our accomplishments to date are:
 Help SAC write and adopt a uniform policy for all students Support and assist in the implementation of recess for all students every day Provide a classroom boost ($1500 per classroom) to instructional teachers and in grades K-5 as well as support staff (Speech, Gifted, OT, VE).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How are donations used?</title>
      <link>/questions/fnse/how-are-donations-used-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/fnse/how-are-donations-used-/</guid>
      <description>All donations to FNSE go directly back into the students, school, and teachers and faculty. Currently we are aiming to raise another $6000 to finish our Boost Program, providing funds for Art, Music, PE and Media Center teachers to spruce up their classrooms. We also like to have funds on hand to support professional development for teachers and field trip support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does FNSE hope to achieve?</title>
      <link>/questions/fnse/what-does-fnse-hope-to-achieve-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/fnse/what-does-fnse-hope-to-achieve-/</guid>
      <description>The mission of FNSE is to partner with North Shore Elementary in their work to ensure it is a dynamic, engaging and successful public school that proudly serves families in the Northeast region of St. Petersburg. We envision that North Shore Elementary is a dynamic, engaging, and successful school that it is a key driver for families and businesses to locate to the area. To that end we hope to be a model for other neighborhoods about how you can engage and support your local public school in mutually beneficial ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When was FNSE created?</title>
      <link>/questions/fnse/fnsecreated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/fnse/fnsecreated/</guid>
      <description>FNSE officially incorporated as a 501&amp;#40;c)(3) in 2015. We have been working together and meeting monthly (more or less) ever since.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>